MD. INZAMUL HUQ

Masters of Social Science

Nikunja-2, Dhaka, Bangladesh

inzamul.huq2000@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/inzamulhuq

+8801742-448686



Career Objective:

To work in your organization of Bangladesh / International in its any department and grow rapidly with increasing responsibilities.

Career Summary:

I'm Skilled in Full Stack Web Development (UX/UI Design, Web Design & Development) and Also good at Admin/Customer Support, Office Skills (Excel, ERP, and GSPN). I have approximately 5 year working experience in different sector. I have prepared myself to work in any type of organization.

Career Summary:

1. Executive, SVC Operations (Logistic & Distribution)

March 2021 to Continue

Department: Customer Care Division

Excel Telecom (Pvt.) Limited - National Distributor of SAMSUNG in Bangladesh

Company Location: Nikunja-2, Khilkhet, Dhaka

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Examine the level of supplies and raw materials to determine shortages.
- Document daily deliveries and shipments to update inventory.
- Prepare a detailed report on inventory operations, stock levels, and adjustments.
- Order new supplies to obtain the best cost-effective deals.
- Maintaining and updating daily records of Good Parts, Spare Parts, faulty parts etc.
- Counting materials in stock.
- Panning to improve upon inventory management or stock control procedures.
- · Stock and distributing supplies, equipment.
- Purchase spare parts from different partners
- Software skills GSPN, ERP, Outlook

2. Junior Officer

June 2020 to February 2021

Department: Customer Care Division

bKash Limited.

Company Location: Shibbari Moar, Khulna Sadar, Khulna

Duties/Responsibilities:

face-to-face customer service

- Ensuring customer satisfaction.
- Actively solving the client's problem.
- Report time to time to the supervisor for complicated issues.

3. Customer Service Representative (CSR)

January 2018 to November 2019 Department: Customer Support

Digicon Technologies Ltd. (GrameenPhone Ltd.)

Company Location: Nikunja-2, Khilkhet, Dhaka

Duties/Responsibilities:

- Inbound call service provide to GP Customer
- Handle incoming calls to the prospective customers pertaining to the Client's business.
- Ensuring customer satisfaction.
- Identify customer needs, clarify information and provide solutions.
- · Actively solving the client's problem.
- Report from time to time to the supervisor for complicated issues.

4. Computer Operator (Admin Support)

January 2015 to December 2017

Department: Administration Division Intelligent Image Management Ltd.

Company Location: DOHS Baridhara, Dhaka

<u>Duties/Responsibilities:</u>

- Data entries from assign by TL
- Checking all Information.
- Make the daily attendant report.
- Other's work assign by management.

Language Proficiency:

Language	Speaking	Listening	Reading	Writing
Bengali	Good	Good	Good	Good
English	Good	Good	Good	Good

Academic Qualifications:

Exam Title	Major	Institute	Results	Passing Year
M.S.S.	Political Science	Govt. Edward	Second Class	2019
		College <u>under of</u>		(2017)
		National University		
B.S.S.	Political Science	Hazi Jamal Uddin	Second Class	2017
(hon's)		College <u>under of</u>		(2015)
		National University		
H.S.C.	Humanities	Mohammed Yasin	First Class	2011
		Degree College		
		under of Rajshahi		
		<u>Board</u>		
S.S.C.	Humanities	Banwarinagar	Second Class	2009
		C.B.P. High School		
		under of Rajshahi		
		<u>Board</u>		

Professional Training:

1. Web Design (Font-end-Design)

Basis Institute of Technology Management (BITM)

Duration: 3Month

Location: BDBL Bhaban, 12 Kawran Bazar, Dhaka -1215. Achieved Skills: HTML, CSS, Raw JavaScript, and Bootstrap.

2. Computer Application (MS Word/Excel/PowerPoint, Photoshop)

B-Nagar Computer Institute

Duration: 3Month

Location: Banwarinagar, Faridpur, Pabna Achieved Skills: MS Word/Excel/PowerPoint

3. UX/UI Design

Creative IT Institute
Duration: 2Month
Location: Online

Achieved Skills: Research, IA, Wireframe, GUI, and Prototype.

4. Web Development (Back-end-Development)

Learning and Earning Projects

Duration: 3Month Location: Online

Achieved Skills: WordPress

Skills:

Admin support

Microsoft Office (essential)

PDF creation and editing

Lead Generation

UX/UI Design

Font-end-Development

Adobe creative suite (essential)

WordPress

Personal Details:

Name : Md. Inzamul Huq

Nick Name : Emon

Father's Name : Hazi Md. Elias Uddin

Mother's Name : Mst. Ismat Ara Date of Birth : 01/11/1992

Gender : Male
Blood Group : O (+ve)
Marital Status : Single
Religion : Islam

Permanente Address : Village-Thanapara(west), PO-Banwarinagar,

PS-Faridpur, District-Pabna

Home Contacts: Mobile +8801716964442 (Father's phone number)

Reference:

No. 1

Name : MD. ZAHIDUL ISLAM Organization : Bashnudhara Group

Designation : AGM

Phone : +8801730323212

Email : zahid0208@gmail.com

No. 2

Name : Himangshu Shakhar Pandit Organization : Excel Telecom (Pvt.) Limited

Designation : Manager

Phone : +88 01713229889

Email : himangshu.log@etcl-bd.com

Declaration:

I do hereby declare that above particulars of information and facts stated are true, correct and complete to the best of my knowledge and belief.